[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 5]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
"Unsoiled Starlight"]
[Original Writer: Shangujun]
Lawyer Shu,
could you treat me to a late-night snack?
Anyway, I'm
already full from working overtime.
Zhuo Yu'an.
Yes?
Has anyone ever told you
that you're pretty strange?
Hmm.
Everyone says I'm exceptionally gifted.
Let me put it this way.
Our first time
was an accident.
But you come to my place
again and again,
what do you mean by that?
Besides,
you just chewed me out
at the company during the day,
and then you showed up at my door again,
coming to wash dishes and cook.
Those who know would say
Zhuo Yu'an runs a company.
Those who don't would think
you learned Sichuan face-changing Opera.
Shu Tinglan.
I'm a person who keeps public
and private matters separate.
I hope we
don't talk about work in private.
If
anything made you misunderstand,
I apologize.
Fine.
If we don't talk about work,
there's even less of a relationship
between us in private
to talk about anything else.
I've said that
we are adults.
We can take responsibility
for our own actions.
Let's part on good terms.
Plus,
I was the one who initiated it that time.
It has nothing to do with you.
Nothing to do with me?
Yeah.
If it wasn't you,
it would have been someone else.
Don't let it weigh on you.
Shu Tinglan,
do you really mean it?
[Zhuoyuan Technology]
The revision direction
of the core terms is fine.
But the risk contingency plan
is not specific enough.
The response levels and trigger mechanisms
should be more clearly defined.
Yes.
For this part,
we will supplement
and refine it immediately.
In addition,
this bid report
[The Bid Report by Hongzheng Law Firm
for Zhuoyuan Technology]
[on the Annual Legal Services Project]
[The Bid Report by Hongzheng Law Firm
for Zhuoyuan Technology]
[on the Annual Legal Services Project]
contains detailed data,
but the industry benchmarking angles
are scattered,
and the conclusion is not focused enough.
The bidding strategy
is also rather conservative,
lacking a striking highlight.
Mr. Zhuo, your insight is spot on.
These parts indeed need improvement.
Lawyer Shu made
an independent attempt this time.
The framework is good.
Our team will do our best
to polish the details.
Lawyer Shu.
Please go ahead, Mr. Zhuo.
I trust Director Xiao's team's ability
to make revisions.
[The Bid Report by Hongzheng Law Firm
for Zhuoyuan Technology]
The technical work on this report
is well done.
[on the Annual Legal Services Project]
But
for the final presentation,
I hope to see
a sharper level of professionalism.
I thought Mr. Zhuo would be busy with work
and wouldn't come again.
The groceries in the fridge
might not be fresh if left any longer.
Mr. Zhuo,
you're so concerned about
the groceries in our fridge.
I'm quite good at
solving specific problems.
For example,
expired ingredients,
or
someone working late into the night
who might not have eaten yet.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
Thanks to Mr. Zhuo,
the proposal was torn to pieces.
But instead, it stirred up
our team's fighting spirit.
Lawyer Xiao said
this is the first step in our progress.
Sounds pretty good,
doesn't it?
Rare to see
you still being nice to me
after working overtime so late
The client has high demands
and strict standards.
That's natural.
We must strive for perfection
and aim to—
What are you doing?
Are you tired today?
Tired or not, I don't want
to work overtime.
I said,
after work,
we don't talk about business.
Shu Tinglan.
You can't make the same mistake twice.
I'll give you three seconds to refuse.
Three
♪ A meteor streaks
across the promises of the past ♪
Two
♪ Memories wither at a touch ♪
♪ Seasons keep changing ♪
♪ I still remember your palm ♪
Shu Tinglan.
Yeah.
The juice down here
expired two weeks ago.
I'll throw it away for you later.
Mm.
And also,
you have
too many drinks in the fridge.
They are high in sugar.
You should drink more water.
It's good for your health.
Mm.
And these eggs,
after a week,
they won't be fresh.
Remember to replace them in time.
Uh-huh.
And the meat in the fridge,
if it's been there for a week,
you need to put it in the freezer,
otherwise...
I didn't even know
Zhuoyuan Technology
was also involved in
food safety management.
What are you making tonight?
You can talk now.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
It's not a state banquet.
Just ordinary chicken wings.
Where's the soy sauce?
Oh.
Here.
Is this the bottle I bought?
Yes.
The one you bought was too big,
so I put it in a water bottle.
I'll go buy a new one.
This is new.
This is new!
You didn't turn off the stove.
Why so troublesome?
Alright.
Let's eat.
Just now,
I was managing our firm's
PR details and quotations sheets.
I'm still considering
whether to include
third-party cooperation cases.
I know little about that.
Trust your own judgment.
Our law firm has a lot of experience
in finance and accounting.
But I'm worried
Zhuoyuan Technology will value
third-party assessment agencies more.
Eat more.
Zhuo Yu'an,
Would it be possible
for you
when the bids are on par
give our firm more consideration?
Why?
Our law firm
really put a lot of effort into this bid.
I've told you—
Okay.
No business talk after work.
Then,
for the sake of
how well we get along in private?
What is our relationship in private?
Party A and...
No.
Calling you a tool
isn't appropriate.
Bed buddies?
How about that?
Shu Tinglan,
what do I, Zhuo Yu'an, to  mean you?
A tool that comes when called
and is thrown away after use?
Well,
if Mr. Zhuo doesn't like it,
you can name it yourself.
I'll go work overtime now.
Okay.
Then bed buddies.
Now I'm going to exercise
my rights as a bed buddy.
Zhuo Yu'an.
I have to work overtime tomorrow.
Tomorrow is the weekend.
No overtime allowed.
Shushu.
Why did you lock the door?
Open the door.
Do you not want me anymore, Shushu?
Shushu.
Why did you lock the door?
Open the door.
Shushu.
Don't go.
Drink.
Drink a bit more.
Come on.
Any more wine?
Drink some more.